<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
  <id>org.kde.ktechlab.desktop</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">KTechLab</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Ktechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">KTechlab</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKTechlabxx</name>
  <summary>IDE for microcontrollers and electronics</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">IDE per a microcontroladors i electrònica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">IDE per a microcontroladors i electrònica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">Entwicklungsumgebung für Mikrocontroller und Elektronik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">IDE for microcontrollers and electronics</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">IDE para microcontroladores y sistemas electrónicos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">Mikrokontrollerite ja elektroonika arenduskeskkond</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Environnement de Développement Intégré pour les microcontrôleurs et l'électronique</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">IDE para microcontroladores e compoñentes electrónicos</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">IDE untuk mikrokontroler dan elektronik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Un IDE per microcontrollori ed elettronica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">마이크로컨트롤러와 전자 회로 IDE</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">IDE (ontwikkelomgeving) voor microcontrollers en elektronica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">IDE dla mikrokontrolerów i elektroniki</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">IDE para micro-controladores e electrónica</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">IDE para microcontroladores e simulador de circuitos eletrônicos.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Interaktivno razvojno okolje za mikrokontrolerje in elektroniko</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">En integrerad utvecklingsmiljö för mikrokontroller och elektronik</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Комплексне середовище розробки для мікроконтролерів та електроніки</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxIDE for microcontrollers and electronicsxx</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      KTechlab is an IDE for microcontrollers and electronics designed to be as easy to use and unintrusive as possible.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El KTechlab és un IDE per a microcontroladors i electrònica dissenyat per a ser tan fàcil d'usar i discret com sigui possible.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">El KTechlab és un IDE per a microcontroladors i electrònica dissenyat per a ser tan fàcil d'usar i discret com siga possible.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">KTechlab is an IDE for microcontrollers and electronics designed to be as easy to use and nonintrusive as possible.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">KTechlab es un entorno de desarrollo integrado para microcontroladores y electrónica diseñado para que sea fácil de usar y lo menos intrusivo posible.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">KTechlab on mikrokontrollerite ja elektroonika arenduskeskkond, mille sihiks on olla võimalikult hõlpsasti kasutatav ja võimalikult vähe kasutaja tegemistesse sekkuv.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Un Environnement de Développement Intégré pour les microcontrôleurs et l'électronique conçu pour être facile à utiliser et aussi peu intrusif que possible.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">KTechlab é un IDE para microcontroladores e compoñentes electrónicos deseñado para ser todo o fácil de usar e non intrusivo posíbel.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">KTechlab adalah sebuah IDE untuk mikrokontroler dan elektronik yang didesain agar mudah digunakan dan tidak seribet mungkin.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">KTechlab è un IDE per microcontrollori ed elettronica progettato per essere semplice da usare e meno invadente possibile.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">KTechlab은 사용하기 쉽게 설계된 마이크로와 전자 회로 IDE입니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">KTechlab is een IDE (ontwikkelomgeving) voor microcontrollers en elektronica ontworpen voor gemakkelijk gebruik en zo weinig opdringerig als mogelijk.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">KTechlab jest IDE (zintegrowanym środowiskiem programistycznym) dla mikrokontrolerów i elektroniki stworzonym, aby być łatwym w użyciu i nie przeszkadzać tam, gdzie tylko jest to możliwe.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O KTechlab é um IDE para micro-controladores e electrónica, desenhado para ser simples de usar e o menos incómodo possível.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O KTechlab é uma IDE para microcontroladores e simulador de circuitos eletrônicos projetado para ser de fácil utilização.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">KTechlab je interaktivno razvojno okolje za mikrokontrolerje in elektroniko, ki je zasnovan tako, da je enostaven za uporabo in čim bolj nevsiljiv.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Ktechlab är en integrerad utvecklingsmiljö för mikrokontroller och elektronik konstruerad för att vara så lättanvänd och lite påträngande som möjligt.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">KTechlab — це комплексне середовище розробки для мікроконтролерів та електроніки, створене якомога простішим у користуванні і ненав’язливим.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKTechlab is an IDE for microcontrollers and electronics designed to be as easy to use and unintrusive as possible.xx</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kenmerken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Wide range of components with editable characteristics</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Gran varietat de components amb característiques modificables</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Gran varietat de components amb característiques modificables</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Wide range of components with editable characteristics</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Amplio abanico de componentes con características editables</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Ulatuslik muudetavate tunnustega komponentide valik</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Gamme large de composants avec des caractéristiques éditables</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Unha gran variedade de compoñentes con características editábeis</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Berbagai macam komponen dengan karakteristik yang dapat diedit</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ampia gamma di componenti con caratteristiche modificabili</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">다양한 구성 요소와 특성 편집 기능</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Brede reeks van componenten met bewerkbare karakteristieken</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wiele części składowych z edytowalnymi charakterystykami</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Gama abrangente de componentes com características editáveis</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Grande variedade de componentes e a possibilidade de alterar suas características</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Širok nabor komponent z značilnostmi, ki jih je mogoče urejati</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Stor mängd komponenter med redigerbara karaktäristika</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Широкий діапазон компонентів із придатними до редагування властивостями.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxWide range of components with editable characteristicsxx</li>
      <li>Visual editor for circuits</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Editor visual per als circuits</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Editor visual per als circuits</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Grafischer Editor für Schaltkreise</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Visual editor for circuits</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Editor de circuitos visual</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Vooluringide visuaalne redaktor</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Éditeur visuel de circuits</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Editor visual de circuítos</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pengedit visual untuk sirkuit</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Editor visuale di circuiti</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">시각적 회로 편집기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Visuele bewerker voor schakelingen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Graficzny edytor dla obwodów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Editor visual de circuitos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Editor visual para circuitos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vizualni urejevalnik za vezja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Visuell editor för kretsscheman</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Візуальний редактор для схем.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxVisual editor for circuitsxx</li>
      <li>Context help for the components</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Ajuda contextual per als components</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Ajuda contextual per als components</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Kontexthilfe für die Komponenten</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Context help for the components</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Ayuda de contexto para los componentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Komponentide kontekstiabi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Aide contextuelle pour les composants</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Axuda contextual para os compoñentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Bantuan konteks untuk komponen</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Aiuto contestuale sui componenti</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">구성 요소에 대한 문맥 도움말</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Contexthulp voor de componenten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Pomoc podręczna dla części składowych</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Ajuda de contexto para os componentes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Aba de ajuda lateral com informações do componente selecionado</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Pomoč v kontekstu komponent</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Sammanhangsberoende hjälp för komponenterna</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Контекстна довідка до компонентів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxContext help for the componentsxx</li>
      <li>Two modes of connector routing: automatic and manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Dos modes d'encaminament per al connector: automàtic i manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Dos modes d'encaminament per al connector: automàtic i manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Two modes of connector routing: automatic and manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Dos modos de rutas de conectores: automático y manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Deux modes de routage de connecteurs : automatique et manuel</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Dous modos de planificación de ruta de conector: automática e manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Dua mode pada penjaluran konektor: otomatis dan manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Due modi di connessione: automatica e manuale</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">커넥터 배치 모드: 자동 및 수동</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Twee manieren van routering van verbindingen: automatisch en handmatig</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Dwa tryby tworzenia ścieżek: samoczynny oraz ręczny</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Dois modos de encaminhamento de ligações: automático e manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Dois modos de ligação: automático e manual</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Dva načina usmerjanja priključkov: samodejni in ročni</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Två sätt att sammankoppla anslutningar: automatisk och manuell</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Два режими маршрутизації з’єднань: автоматичний і ручний.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTwo modes of connector routing: automatic and manualxx</li>
      <li>Several ways to define the PIC logic: assembly code, Microbe (own high level programming language) code, C code, and visual FlowCode</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Diverses maneres de definir el PIC lògic: codi en assemblador, codi en Microbe (llenguatge de programació propi d'alt nivell), codi en C i FlowCode visual</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Diverses maneres de definir el PIC lògic: codi en assemblador, codi en Microbe (llenguatge de programació propi d'alt nivell), codi en C i FlowCode visual</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Several ways to define the PIC logic: assembly code, Microbe (own high level programming language) code, C code, and visual FlowCode</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Diversos modos de definir la lógica del PIC: código ensamblador, código Microbe (lenguaje de programación propio de alto nivel), código C y FlowCode visual</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Plusieurs façons de définir la logiques « PIC » : code assembleur, code Microbe (langage de programmation de haut niveau autonome), code « C » et code visuel « FlowCode »</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Varias formas de definir a lóxica de PIC: código de ensamblador, código de Microbe (linguaxe de programación propia de alto nivel), código de C e FlowCode visual</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Beberapa cara untuk menentukan logika PIC: kode perakitan, kode Microbe (bahasa pemrograman tingkat tinggi), kode C, dan FlowCode visual</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Molti modi di definire la logica del PIC: codice assembly, codice Microbe (un proprio linguaggio di programmazione ad alto livello), codice C e FlowCode visuale</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">PIC 논리 회로를 정의하는 여러 방법: 어셈블리 코드, Microbe 코드(자체 고수준 프로그래밍 언어), C 코드, 시각적 FlowCode</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verschillende manieren om de PIC-logica te definiëren: assembly code, Microbe (eigen hoog niveau programmeertaal) code, C code en visuele FlowCode</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kilka sposobów określania logiki PIC: kod złożenia, kod Microbe (własny wysoko-poziomowy język programowania), kod C oraz graficzny kod przepływu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Diversas formas de definir a lógica do PIC: código em Assembly, código em Microbe (linguagem de programação própria de alto nível), código em C e fluxogramas visuais.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Várias maneiras de definir a lógica PIC:  código assembly  , código microbe (linguagem de programação de alto nível própria), código C e FlowCode visual</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Več načinov za določitev logike PIC: koda montaže, Microbe (lastni visoko nivojski programski jezik) koda, koda v C in vizual FlowCode</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flera olika sätt att definiera PIC-logik: assemblerkod, Microbe-kod (eget högnivåprogramspråk), C-kod och visuell FlowCode</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Декілька способів визначення логіки PIC: асемблерний код, Microbe (власна високорівнева мова програмування), код C та візуальний FlowCode.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSeveral ways to define the PIC logic: assembly code, Microbe (own high level programming language) code, C code, and visual FlowCodexx</li>
      <li>Interconversion of the programming code between supported languages</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Interconversió del codi de programació entre els llenguatges admesos</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Interconversió del codi de programació entre els llenguatges admesos</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Interconversion of the programming code between supported languages</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Conversión interna del código de programación entre los lenguajes permitidos</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Programmikoodi vaba teisendamine toetatud programmeerimiskeelte vahel</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Interconversion de code de programmation entre langages pris en charge</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Conversión do código de programación entre as linguaxes permitidas</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Interkonversi kode pemrograman antara bahasa yang didukung</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Interconversione del codice di programmazione fra i linguaggi supportati</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">지원하는 언어간 프로그래밍 코드 변환</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Onderlinge conversie van de programmeercode tussen ondersteunde talen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Przekształcanie kodu pomiędzy obsługiwanymi językami</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Conversão do código programado entre as linguagens suportadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Possibilidade de conversão entre as linguagens suportadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Medsebojna pretvorba programske kode med podprtimi jeziki</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Konvertering mellan programkoden mellan språk som stöds</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Взаємне перетворення програмного коду між підтримуваними мовами.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxInterconversion of the programming code between supported languagesxx</li>
      <li>Inbuilt debugger</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Depurador incorporat</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Depurador incorporat</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Inbuilt debugger</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Depurador integrado</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Sisseehitatud silur</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Débogueur intégré</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Depurador integrado</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Debugger bawaan</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Debugger interno</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">내장 디버거</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Ingebouwde debugger</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wbudowany program diagnostyczny</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Depurador incorporado</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Depurador embutido</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Vgrajen razhroščevalnik</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">inbyggd avlusare</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вбудований засіб діагностики.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxInbuilt debuggerxx</li>
      <li>Simulation with oscilloscope and probes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Simulació amb oscil·loscopi i sondes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Simulació amb oscil·loscopi i sondes</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Simulation with oscilloscope and probes</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Simulación con osciloscopio y sondas</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Simulation avec oscilloscope et sondes</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Simulación de osciloscopios e sondas</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Simulasi dengan osiloskop dan probe</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Simulazione con oscilloscopio e con sonde</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">오실로스코프와 프로브 시뮬레이션</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Simulatie met oscilloscope en probes</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Symulacje przy użyciu oscyloskopu i mierników</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Simulação com osciloscópios e sondas</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Simulação com osciloscópio e sondas</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Simulacija z osciloskopom in sondami</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Simulering med oscilloskop och prober</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Імітація за допомогою осцилоскопа і зондів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxSimulation with oscilloscope and probesxx</li>
      <li>Uploading the assembly code to PIC using hardware programmer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Puja el codi en assemblador al PIC emprant el programador de maquinari</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Puja el codi en assemblador al PIC emprant el programador de maquinari</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Uploading the assembly code to PIC using hardware programmer</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Envío del código ensamblador al PIC usando el programador hardware</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Chargement du code assembleur vers le « PIC » en utilisant le programmateur matériel</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Enviando o código ensamblador a PIC usando o programador de soporte físico</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Mengunggah kode perakitan ke PIC menggunakan pemrogram hardware</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Caricamento del codice assembly nel PIC con un programmatore hardware</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">하드웨어 프로그래머로 PIC에 어셈블리 코드 업로드</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Uploaden van de assembly code naar PIC met hardware programmeerder</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wysyłanie kodu złożenia na PIC przy użyciu sprzętowego programatora</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Envio do código em Assembly para o PIC, usando um programador por 'hardware'</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Gravação do código Assembly no PIC usando os programadores de hardware</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Nalaganje zbirne kode v PIC s pomočjo strojnega programatorja</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Uppladdning av assemblerkoden till en PIC med användning av hårdvaruprogrammerare</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Вивантаження асемблерного коду на PIC за допомогою апаратного програматора.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxUploading the assembly code to PIC using hardware programmerxx</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <image>https://userbase.kde.org/images.userbase/e/e6/Ktechlab_screen.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://userbase.kde.org/Special:myLanguage/KTechlab</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=ktechlab</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>ktechlab</binary>
  </provides>
</component>
